<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Panic Button</string>
    <string name="start_meditation">START MEDITATION</string>
    <string name="stop_meditation">STOP MEDITATION</string>
    <string name="heading">Welcome to Stress Release App</string>
    <string name="description">Meditation is generally considered a safe activity, especially at the beginning levels. At these levels, it is mainly a practice in deep stillness, breathing and presence. <br /><br /> \n\n
        However, advanced levels of meditation can require a willingness to use your powers of concentration in order to engage in self-study and examination.<br /><br /> \n\n
        If you feel you might be uncomfortable engaging in this kind of self-examination, then we ask that you do not proceed beyond the beginning level until you feel secure and comfortable with proceeding further If you have a history of mental illness, then please consult with your health care provider before learning meditation.<br /><br />\n\n
        This is not to say that meditation will be harmful to you, but it’s better to be on the safe side. Please be aware that we make no claim to be any kind of psychologist, therapist, counselor or medical professional.<br /><br />\n\n
        Anything we say or write should be understood as our own opinion and not an expression of professional advice or prescription.<br /><br />\n\n
        You are entirely responsible for how you choose to understand, misunderstand, use or misuse any of our writings or communications. We can accept no responsibility for any adverse affects, direct or indirect, that may result from your use of the information on this website and guided meditations or in any of our communications.<br /><br />\n\n
        Furthermore, we make no guarantees that any of the information or practices on this website and guided meditations will function in any particular way for you.<br /><br />\n\n
        By using this website and guided meditations, you agree that you use the information contained herein entirely at your own discretion. Listen to your body.<br /><br />\n\n
        Modify what you need to. Own your practice. Feel empowered and easeful in your Week of Zen.P.S. Don’t meditate while driving.<br /><br />\n\n
</string>
</resources>